I bought a duster, but it was too big and too long
like this.  Don't worry, Mumun is here to teach you
modifications to make it cool, Shy.  But
this is for those who want to.  Those who
don't want to can skip.  First we
cut the bottom part.  This doesn't need to be
measured, just be reckless.  Continue
cutting the top part to the hands.  Well,
the next one is the same.  Now sew the
middle part and then pull the thread
until it wrinkles like this.  Then the
side parts are reduced to follow the
body size.  The bottom part is cut a little
more.  Then we'll use the remaining pieces from the
first cut to make a raffle, Beb.
Then we put it on as a decoration at the
bottom of Clarshy's blond skirt.
Also attach a raffle to the collar from the
remaining fabric.  Oh, that's it.
How about it, guys?  So it's really cool, right?  Mumun is like that
.  Well, now it's your turn to
try it too.  Gasla.
Yeah.